A Guide to the Davi Det Hompson Papers, 1969-1988
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Davi Det Hompson Papers, 1969-1988
M 251
8 linear feet
David E. Thompson
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for use without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated to the department by Mr. Thompson in 1988 and 1991.
Biographical/Historical Information
David E. Thompson / Davi Det Hompson (1939-December 8, 1996) was a Richmond artist who exhibited widely in the United States and Europe. His work is included in the collections of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts; the Kansas City Art Institute; the New Museum, Museum of Modern Art, and Franklin Furnace in New York City; the Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art; the Archive Sohm in Germany; and the Groninger Museum in the Netherlands. He is best known for creating book art, mail art, and text-based paintings based on the principles of the Fluxus and Dada movements. His pen name, Davi Det Hompson, illustrates Thompson's interest in manipulating the structure and meaning of the written word.
David Thompson was born in Sharon, PA. He received his Bachelor's degree from Anderson College in Indiana and his Master's of Fine Arts from Indiana University. He spent the last twenty years of his life as an active member of the Richmond arts community. He was a founding member of Richmond's 1708 East Main Street gallery, served on the Board of Directors of the Richmond Arts Council from 1983-86, and taught at Virginia Commonwealth University. In 1979, Thompson served on a volunteer committee that was instrumental in establishing the Book Art Collection in Special Collections and Archives at Virginia Commonwealth University's James Branch Cabell Library. He was married to Nancy Kunkle Thompson, a professor in Virginia Commonwealth University's Department of Crafts.
Scope and Content Information
The bulk of the collection includes correspondence in the form of letters, mail art, and poetry to and from Davi Det Hompson from 1969 through 1988. The inclusion of typed copies of letters from Hompson adds a dimension of exchange to the correspondences in the collection. Notable exchanges are documented between Davi Det Hompson and artists, Anna Banana, Fletcher Copp, David Sucec, and Alice Aycock; and poets, Madeline Gins, Lyn Hejinian, Richard Craven, and Dick Higgins. The content of the correspondences focuses on Hompson's ideas about art, collaborative efforts, exhibitions and other projects. The collection also includes announcements for art shows along with newsletters and fanzines produced by art groups such as General Idea and W.O.R.K.S. Four folders are dedicated to an exhibition of mail art and performance art held at Virginia Commonwealth University in 1973 titled International Cyclopedia of Plans and Occurrences. The exhibition was curated by Davi Det Hompson and included submissions of mail art from over twenty different countries.
The collection also includes two pieces of book art in completed form accompanied by various drafts. One piece is titled, "For breakfast I'll have, oh, two slices of dry toast and a cup of hot water." The second piece is titled, "You know it has to be a hairpiece." Oversize materials include original photography, drawings, posters and other art works by Davi Det Hompson and various artists.
Arrangement
Arrangement
Collection is arranged in three series.
Organization
Series I--Correspondence (1969-1988) Series II--Book Art Materials (c. 1977) Series III--Oversize Materials ( 1970-73)
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence
  - A Space 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1.1)
  - Aarhus Museum of Art, n.d. 1975-1978 (Box-folder 1.2)
  - Associated Art Publishers Network (AAPN), n.d. 1978-1981 (Box-folder 1.3)
  - Aiee Magazine 1975-1978 (Box-folder 1.4)
  - Ackerman, Al 1974-1975 (Box-folder 1.5)
  - Aknai, Sandor, n.d. (Box-folder 1.6)
  - Akumulatory Gallery, n.d. (Box-folder 1.7)
  - Alarm (M. Kundeins) Analog (fishbien), n.d. 1975-1979 (Box-folder 1.8)
  - Albrecht, D. 1973 (Box-folder 1.9)
  - Alger, Horatio 1976 (Box-folder 1.10)
  - Alocco 1970, 1973 (Box-folder 1.11)
  - Altmann, n.d. (Box-folder 1.12)
  - Amiard, Bernard, n.d. 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1.13)
  - Andersen, E., n.d. (Box-folder 1.14)
  - Ant Farm, n.d. (Box-folder 1.15)
  - Antin, Eleanor, n.d. (Box-folder 1.16)
  - Appalachian Journal 1974 (Box-folder 1.17)
  - Applebroog, Ida 1977 (Box-folder 1.18)
  - Applewhite, Anne 1977 (Box-folder 1.19)
  - Aptaker, Ken 1978 (Box-folder 1.20)
  - Archive Small Press and Communication 1977 (Box-folder 1.21)
  - Arginteanu, Judy 1978 (Box-folder 1.22)
  - Aquino, Angelo de 1973 (Box-folder 1.23)
  - Ardo, Karl 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1.24)
  - Arnason, J.G. 1973 (Box-folder 1.25)
  - Art Hoax--Gangster 1974 (Box-folder 1.26)
  - Art-Rite Magazine, n.d. (Box-folder 1.27)
  - Art and Society Book (Daniel Dewaele), n.d. (Box-folder 1.28)
  - Askin, W, n.d. (Box-folder 1.29)
  - Assumpcao, Ismael 1975 (Box-folder 1.30)
  - Atchley, Dana, n.d. 1973-1980 (Box-folder 1.31)
  - Attalai, Gabor 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1.32)
  - Augustine, Jane 1973 (Box-folder 1.33)
  - Avias-Mission, A., n.d. (Box-folder 1.34)
  - Aycock, Alice 1972 (Box-folder 1.35)
  - Baldessari, John, n.d. (Box-folder 1.36)
  - Banana, Anna, n.d. 1972-1976 (Box-folder 1.37)
  - Baron (George Fredmertz) 1978 (Box-folder 2.1)
  - Below, Peter 1974-1978 (Box-folder 2.2)
  - Bennecke, Reinhard, n.d. 1975 (Box-folder 2.3)
  - Berg, Tom 1973-1979 (Box-folder 2.4)
  - Bergsson, G. 1973 (Box-folder 2.5)
  - Beveren, Peter van 1973-1978 (Box-folder 2.6)
  - Bienvenue, Marcella 1975 (Box-folder 2.7)
  - Bishop, Pat 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2.8)
  - Bisson_Millet, Paule-Leon 1986 (Box-folder 2.9)
  - Bjorklund, Lee, n.d. (Box-folder 2.10)
  - Blitz Information 1975 (Box-folder 2.11)
  - Bon-Bon 1973 (Box-folder 2.12)
  - Bonzai Bob 1974 (Box-folder 2.13)
  - Book Bus 1978 (Box-folder 2.14)
  - Bottinelli, Bickhard 1974 (Box-folder 2.15)
  - Bowles, Jerry G. 1971 (Box-folder 2.16)
  - Braja, Regina 1974 (Box-folder 2.17)
  - Brendt, Frank 1978 (Box-folder 2.18)
  - Briers, David 1972, 1975 (Box-folder 2.19)
  - Broom (Bill Gordon), n.d. 1977 (Box-folder 2.20)
  - Brown, Jean 1972-1982 (Box-folder 2.21)
  - Bruhns, Fred 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2.22)
  - Bruscky, Paulo 1975-1978 (Box-folder 2.23)
  - Bumbershoot 1973 (Box-folder 2.24)
  - Byerley, Gerald 1973-1979 (Box-folder 2.25)
  - Bzdok, Henryk 1977 (Box-folder 2.26)
  - C (Craven), Richard, n.d. 1972-1980 (Box-folder 2.27)
  - Cairns, Phyllis n.d. (Box-folder 2.28)
  - California 1975 (Box-folder 2.29)
  - Carrier, Loran 1975 (Box-folder 2.30)
  - Carrion, Ulises, n.d. 1975-1981 (Box-folder 2.31)
  - Carter, Paul, n.d. 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3.1)
  - Caterino, Phil 1975 (Box-folder 3.2)
  - Cavellini, Guglleimo Achille, n.d. 1976-1978 (Box-folder 3.3)
  - Center--C. Berge 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3.4)
  - Central Tool 1973, 1976 (Box-folder 3.5)
  - Christobal, Richard (Orgon) 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3.6)
  - Church of the SubGenius, The 1981, 1982, n.d. (Box-folder 3.7)
  - Chusid, Dan 1981 (Box-folder 3.8)
  - Cicatelli, Carlo G. 1975 (Box-folder 3.9)
  - Cohen, Ryosuke n.d. (Box-folder 3.10)
  - Colab 4, n.d. 1973 (Box-folder 3.11)
  - Copp. Fletcher 1973-1976 (Box-folder 3.12)
  - Corris, Michael, n.d. 1984 (Box-folder 3.13)
  - Counterpoint 1973 (Box-folder 3.14)
  - Cover Mail-Art Show 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3.15)
  - Corcoran (F. Fralin) 1976 (Box-folder 3.16)
  - Crane, Mike 1980 (Box-folder 3.17)
  - Crowcroft, Ron, n.d. 1973-1981 (Box-folder 3.18)
  - Crozier, Robin, n.d. 1973-1981 (Box-folder 3.19)
  - Crumming, Robert, n.d. 1975 (Box-folder 3.20)
  - Cuttlefish 1978 (Box-folder 3.21)
  - Dadaland Press, n.d. 1973-1978 (Box-folder 3.22)
  - Danon, Betty 1978 (Box-folder 3.23)
  - Davies, Richard 1976-1982 (Box-folder 4.1)
  - Davis, Delia 1972 (Box-folder 4.2)
  - Davis, Russ, n.d. 1975-1978 (Box-folder 4.3)
  - de Rook, G.J., n.d. 1972-1978 (Box-folder 4.4)
  - Deisler, Guillermo, n.d. (Box-folder 4.5)
  - Dejasu, Lee 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4.6)
  - Delva, Jean-Louis 1976 (Box-folder 4.7)
  - Devree 1971 (Box-folder 4.8)
  - D'Hondt, Roger 1987 (Box-folder 4.9)
  - Dogmatic, Irene, n.d. 1976-1978 (Box-folder 4.10)
  - Dombrowski, Gerard, n.d. 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4.11)
  - Dov or-Ner 1973, 1975 (Box-folder 4.12)
  - Dowd, John, n.d. 1973 (Box-folder 4.13)
  - Dragoni, Ferruccio, n.d. (Box-folder 4.14)
  - Dreva, Jerry 1977-1980 (Box-folder 4.15)
  - D'Ziner, Johnny, n.d. (Box-folder 4.16)
  - Ecart 1974-1978 (Box-folder 4.17)
  - Espy 1974 (Box-folder 4.18)
  - Farley, William, n.d. (Box-folder 4.19)
  - Fat City, n.d. 1972 (Box-folder 4.20)
  - Felluss Gallery 1978 (Box-folder 4.21)
  - Felts, Nill, n.d. 1973-1978 (Box-folder 4.22)
  - Fergusson, Frank 1977 (Box-folder 4.23)
  - Film, Mike, n.d. 4.24 (Box-folder 4.24)
  - Fischer 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4.25)
  - Fish, Pat 1980 (Box-folder 4.26)
  - Flynt, Henry 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4.27)
  - Fodor, Charles, n.d. (Box-folder 4.28)
  - Ford, M.L. 1978 (Box-folder 4.29)
  - Four hundred and ninety-one (491) Magazine, n.d. 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4.30)
  - Francke, Cees (Spudz) 1977 (Box-folder 4.31)
  - Frank, Peter 1976-1980 (Box-folder 4.32)
  - Franklin Furnace, n.d. 1977-1980 (Box-folder 5.1)
  - Franks, David, n.d. 1969-1982 (Box-folder 5.2)
  - Fridfinnsonn, Hreinn 1973 (Box-folder 5.3)
  - Friedman, Ken 1981-1982 (Box-folder 5.4)
  - Froese, Dieter 1973-1975 (Box-folder 5.5)
  - Fujiwara, Kazumichi, n.d. (Box-folder 5.6)
  - Game Preserve (P. Kekich) 1975 (Box-folder 5.7)
  - Garringer, Jeffery 1974-1976 (Box-folder 5.8)
  - General Idea, n.d. 1972 (Box-folder 5.9)
  - George in Georgia 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5.10)
  - Gerz, Jochen 1972-1973 (Box-folder 5.11)
  - Gette, Paul-Armand, n.d. 1972 (Box-folder 5.12)
  - Giaccari, Luciano 1976 (Box-folder 5.13)
  - Gifreu 1977 (Box-folder 5.14)
  - Gilbert, Gerry 1972-1975 (Box-folder 5.15)
  - Gilliland, Mark 1974-1978 (Box-folder 5.16)
  - Gins, Madeline 1971 (Box-folder 5.17)
  - Ginzburg, Carlos, n.d. 1971 (Box-folder 5.18)
  - Glassworks (Betty Bressi), n.d. 1975-1978 (Box-folder 5.19)
  - Glover, Hank 1973 (Box-folder 5.20)
  - Glusberg, Jorge 1975-1978 (Box-folder 5.21)
  - Goldstein, Richard 1971 (Box-folder 5.22)
  - Golikoff, Edwin, n.d. 1971 (Box-folder 5.23)
  - Gonsalez, Haroldo 1973, 1976 (Box-folder 5.24)
  - Gosling, John 1973-1974 (Box-folder 5.25)
  - Graham, C.P. 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6.1)
  - Graham, P.G. 1977 (Box-folder 6.2)
  - Greenberger, David 1979-1980 (Box-folder 6.3)
  - Groh, Klaus, n.d. 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6.4)
  - Grygar, Milan 1970-1971 (Box-folder 6.5)
  - Hahn, Horst 1976 (Box-folder 6.6)
  - Hall, Suzanne 1976 (Box-folder 6.7)
  - Hambleton, Richard Art, n.d. (Box-folder 6.8)
  - Hap, Bela, n.d. (Box-folder 6.9)
  - Heenehan, Jim, n.d. (Box-folder 6.10)
  - Heidsieck, Bernard 1962, 1970, 1978 (Box-folder 6.11)
  - Hejinian, Lyn n.d. 1974-1977 (Box-folder 6.12)
  - Held, John (Box-folder 6.13)
  - Hendricks, Geoff, n.d. 1969-1980 (Box-folder 6.14)
  - Hickman, Ken 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6.15)
  - Hidalgo, Juan 1973 (Box-folder 6.16)
  - Higgins, Dick, n.d. 1967-1980 (Box-folder 6.17)
  - Hirshorn, Anne Sue 1975-1977 (Box-folder 6.18)
  - Hoffberg, Judith 1978-1980 (Box-folder 6.19)
  - Holy Cow 1973 (Box-folder 6.20)
  - Horn, Stu 1974 (Box-folder 6.21)
  - Hosier, Tom, n.d. (Box-folder 6.22)
  - Houck 1976 (Box-folder 6.23)
  - Howe, Nelson 1972-1974 (Box-folder 6.24)
  - Hundertmark, Armin, n.d. 1978-1980 (Box-folder 6.25)
  - Limura, Taka 1972 (Box-folder 6.26)
  - Illardo, Ronald 1974 (Box-folder 6.27)
  - Image Bank, n.d. 1972-1980 (Box-folder 7.1)
  - Impact 1974 (Box-folder 7.2)
  - Impulse (Eldon Garnet) 1978-1979 (Box-folder 7.3)
  - Inch Art 1974-1976 (Box-folder 7.4)
  - Intermedia (Ed Varney) 1976-1980 (Box-folder 7.5)
  - Ittner, John, n.d. 1976-1978 (Box-folder 7.6)
  - Jones, Chris 1977 (Box-folder 7.7)
  - J.P.L. Gallery 1976, 1978 (Box-folder 7.8)
  - Kalivoda, Peter, n.d. (Box-folder 7.9)
  - Kalkman, Hans-Werner 1972-1974 (Box-folder 7.10)
  - Kansas City, n.d. (Box-folder 7.11)
  - Karoly, Matz, n.d. (Box-folder 7.12)
  - Kasper, Michael 1984 (Box-folder 7.13)
  - Kearney, John 1973-1974 (Box-folder 7.14)
  - Kelly, Robert, n.d. (Box-folder 7.15)
  - Kemeny, Tomaso 1972 (Box-folder 7.16)
  - Kent, Caroline, n.d. (Box-folder 7.17)
  - Kevorkian, Karen 1976-1977 (Box-folder 7.18)
  - Klivar, Miroslav, n.d. 1972-1974 (Box-folder 7.19)
  - Ko de Jonge, C.D.M. 1976, 1978 (Box-folder 7.20)
  - Koche, Donald 1978 (Box-folder 7.21)
  - Kocman, J.H. 1973-1976 (Box-folder 7.22)
  - Korell 1978 (Box-folder 7.23)
  - Korn, Henry J. 1972-1978 (Box-folder 7.24)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, n.d. 1971-1978 (Box-folder 7.25)
  - Kozlowski, Jaroslaw 1973 (Box-folder 7.26)
  - Larsen, Rose 1985-1988 (Box-folder 7.27)
  - Laughing Bear 1971-1972 (Box-folder 7.28)
  - Laurer, n.d. (Box-folder 7.29)
  - Lausten, Thorbjorn, n.d. 1973 (Box-folder 7.30)
  - Legendy, Peter 1972 (Box-folder 7.31)
  - Levine, Sherrie 1977 (Box-folder 7.32)
  - LeWitt, Sol 1974 (Box-folder 7.33)
  - Lieberman, Ira and Linda 1972 (Box-folder 7.34)
  - Lippard, Lucy 1972, 1974 (Box-folder 7.35)
  - Lomholt Formular Press, n.d. 1978-1980 (Box-folder 8.1)
  - Lory, Ekkehard 1975, 1977 (Box-folder 8.2)
  - Lowie, Nicholas 1988 (Box-folder 8.3)
  - Luigetti, Serse 1982, n.d. (Box-folder 8.4)
  - Magalhaes, Odair 1975-1976 (Box-folder 8.5)
  - Magratten, Davey 1974 (Box-folder 8.6)
  - Magura, Carolyn 1986 (Box-folder 8.6)
  - Mailart (Box-folder 8.8)
  - Maker (McAuley) 1976, 1978 (Box-folder 8.9)
  - Mallander, J.O. 1973 (Box-folder 8.10)
  - La Mamelle, n.d. 1977-1978 (Box-folder 8.11)
  - Mango Dave 1975 (Box-folder 8.12)
  - Marcus, Aaron 1972 (Box-folder 8.13)
  - Marioni, Tom, n.d. (Box-folder 8.14)
  - Martin, Gary 1979 (Box-folder 8.15)
  - Matthews, Joan 1973-1978 (Box-folder 8.16)
  - Mayor, David (Beau Geste Press), n.d. 1971-1980 (Box-folder 8.17)
  - McCann, Richard 1976 (Box-folder 8.18)
  - McCool, Linda 1972 (Box-folder 8.19)
  - McCord, Maryann, n.d. 1970-1971 (Box-folder 8.20)
  - McLennahan 1974 (Box-folder 8.21)
  - Meissner, Susan 1975 (Box-folder 8.22)
  - Mew, Tommy 1978 (Box-folder 9.1)
  - Midland Group Gallery 1973 (Box-folder 9.2)
  - Miler, Karel 1973 (Box-folder 9.3)
  - Miller, David 1985 (Box-folder 9.4)
  - Montana Rose 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9.5)
  - Moorman, Charlotte 1975 (Box-folder 9.6)
  - Morrissey, Stephen 1974-1975 (Box-folder 9.7)
  - Mosby, George 1978, 1980, 1989 (Box-folder 9.8)
  - Motoyuki, Ito 1971 (Box-folder 9.9)
  - Museum of temporary Art (MOTA--Janet Schmukal) 1977 (Box-folder 9.10)
  - Nakajima, Yoshio 1972 (Box-folder 9.11)
  - Nannucci, Maurizio 1978 (Box-folder 9.12)
  - Nations, Opal, n.d. 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9.13)
  - Nemec, Rudolph 1972 (Box-folder 9.14)
  - New Reform 1974-1978 (Box-folder 9.15)
  - New York Corres-Sponge Dance 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9.16)
  - Newman, Ira, n.d. 1969-1980 (Box-folder 9.17)
  - Nikolic, Jean 1972, 1975 (Box-folder 9.18)
  - Nimis Project (Lars Vilks) 1984 (Box-folder 9.19)
  - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design 1972 (Box-folder 9.20)
  - Nutty, Michael 1976 (Box-folder 9.21)
  - Nuttall, Jeff 1973 (Box-folder 9.22)
  - Occu-Pants, n.d. (Box-folder 9.23)
  - Ockerse, Tom, n.d. 1970-1981 (Box-folder 10.1)
  - Ogust, Richard 1985 (Box-folder 10.2)
  - Oisteanu, Valery 1975 (Box-folder 10.3)
  - Opening Press, n.d. (Box-folder 10.4)
  - O'Reilly, Peaches 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10.5)
  - Ossorno, M.H. de 1975 (Box-folder 10.6)
  - Padin, Clemente, n.d. 1969-1976 (Box-folder 10.7)
  - Partum, Ewa, n.d. (Box-folder 10.8)
  - Pattengill, n.d. (Box-folder 10.9)
  - Patterson, Wynnelle 1983 (Box-folder 10.10)
  - Pechter, Paul 1972 (Box-folder 10.11)
  - Pedersen, Knud 1979 (Box-folder 10.12)
  - Peli, Romano 1977-1980, 1982 (Box-folder 10.13)
  - Pereira, Teresinka 1975 (Box-folder 10.14)
  - Perfetti, Michele 1976 (Box-folder 10.15)
  - Phillips, Michael J. 1972, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.16)
  - Pie, Elroy 1976-1979 (Box-folder 10.17)
  - Pinkston, Howell 1973-1974, 1978 (Box-folder 10.18)
  - Plans and Occurrences 1973 (Box-folder 11.1)
  - Plans and Occurences Letters and art (1 of 3) (Box-folder 11.2)
  - Plans and Occurences Letters and art (2 of 3) (Box-folder 11.3)
  - Plans and Occurrences Letters and art (3 of 3) (Box-folder 11.4)
  - Plaza, Julio 1973 (Box-folder 11.5)
  - Primer (Ron Wray) 1976-1978 (Box-folder 11.6)
  - Prillman, Jerry, n.d. 1980 (Box-folder 11.7)
  - Professor Plum 1982 (Box-folder 11.8)
  - Plunkt/Data 1977-1978 (Box-folder 11.9)
  - Queenana, Joe 1981-1982 (Box-folder 11.10)
  - Rabbit Pellets 1974 (Box-folder 11.11)
  - Rapeport, Stuart 1973-1977 (Box-folder 11.12)
  - Reese, Marshall 1981 (Box-folder 11.13)
  - Reid, Terry 1972 (Box-folder 11.14)
  - Reynolds, Carol 1974 (Box-folder 11.15)
  - Richman, Gary, n.d. 1972-1979 (Box-folder 12.1)
  - Riddle, James, n.d. 1972-1979 (Box-folder 12.2)
  - Rigal, Christain 1988 (Box-folder 12.3)
  - Romano, Vincet 1973 (Box-folder 12.4)
  - Root, David 1978 (Box-folder 12.5)
  - Rosenberg, Marilyn 1978, 1980 (Box-folder 12.6)
  - Rosolowicz, Jeryz, n.d. (Box-folder 12.7)
  - Roth, Diter, n.d. (Box-folder 12.8)
  - Rubber Stamp Exhibition 1975 (Box-folder 12.9)
  - Ruhe, Henry, n.d. 1973-1976 (Box-folder 12.10)
  - Runnells, Helen, n.d. 1975-1976 (Box-folder 12.11)
  - Running Dog Press (Mike Crane), n.d. 1976-1980 (Box-folder 12.12)
  - Salt Lick Press, n.d. (Box-folder 12.13)
  - Saroyan, Aram 1971 (Box-folder 12.14)
  - Scherm, Gerd, n.d. 1972 (Box-folder 12.15)
  - Scholtz, Christain 1974, 1978 (Box-folder 12.16)
  - Schwind, J., n.d. 1972 (Box-folder 12.17)
  - Sharp, Willoughby 1974 (Box-folder 12.18)
  - Shohachio, Takahashi 1973 (Box-folder 12.19)
  - Sikora, Rudolf 1973 (Box-folder 13.1)
  - Silveiria, Regina, n.d. (Box-folder 13.2)
  - Skelbye, Poul, n.d. (Box-folder 13.3)
  - Sky Mail 1973, 1975 (Box-folder 13.4)
  - Slorp, John 1972, 1975 (Box-folder 13.5)
  - Sluj International 1974-1978 (Box-folder 13.6)
  - Smith, Kim 1976 (Box-folder 13.7)
  - Smith, Larry 1983 (Box-folder 13.8)
  - Smith, Pauline 1975, 1977 (Box-folder 13.9)
  - Solt, Mary Ellen 1972 (Box-folder 13.10)
  - Sohm (archiv) 1976-1978 (Box-folder 13.11)
  - Sondheim, Alan, n.d. (Box-folder 13.12)
  - Sorensen, William Louis 1970 (Box-folder 13.13)
  - Souza, Al 1973-1978 (Box-folder 13.14)
  - Spatola, Adriano 1973, 1976 (Box-folder 13.15)
  - Spiegelman, Lon 1978 (Box-folder 13.16)
  - Stsek, Rolf 1970 (Box-folder 13.17)
  - Stake, Chuck 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13.18)
  - Staklik, Jan 1970 (Box-folder 13.19)
  - Stecyk, C.R., n.d. (Box-folder 13.20)
  - Stembera, Petr, n.d. (Box-folder 13.21)
  - Stempelplaats, n.d. 1978-1979 (Box-folder 13.22)
  - Stokes, Telfer 1985 (Box-folder 13.23)
  - Sucec, David 1972-1980 (Box-folder 13.24)
  - Summers, Rod, n.d. 1976 (Box-folder 14.1)
  - Sweenen, Peter n.d. (Box-folder 14.2)
  - Tatkalo-Eskola, I.J., n.d. (Box-folder 14.3)
  - Tavenner, Patricia 1972-1973, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 14.4)
  - Tepper, Irv 1973 (Box-folder 14.5)
  - Terji, Nim Aichat 1975 (Box-folder 14.6)
  - Thompson, Nic 1976, 1978 (Box-folder 14.7)
  - Todorovic, Miroljeb 1973 (Box-folder 14.8)
  - Torchia, Richard, n.d. 1982 (Box-folder 14.9)
  - Tot, Endre 1972-1976 (Box-folder 14.10)
  - Troy, David 1973-1975 (Box-folder 14.11)
  - T.R.UTHCO 1977-1981 (Box-folder 14.12)
  - Tucker, Wayland 1980 (Box-folder 14.13)
  - Urban, Janos, n.d. 1973-1976 (Box-folder 14.14)
  - Urin, Viktor 1975 (Box-folder 14.15)
  - URTHKIN 1975-1977 (Box-folder 14.16)
  - Valier, Biron, n.d. (Box-folder 14.17)
  - Valoch, Jiri 1972-1973 (Box-folder 14.18)
  - Vandenburgh, A. (Box-folder 15.1)
  - Vansen, Leslie 1974 (Box-folder 15.2)
  - Vargen 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15.3)
  - Varney, Ed 1981 (Box-folder 15.4)
  - Vazan, William 1972 (Box-folder 15.5)
  - Video Bag 1974 (Box-folder 15.6)
  - Vigo, E.A., n.d. (Box-folder 15.7)
  - Vogrin, Hak 1972 (Box-folder 15.8)
  - Whoever 1973 (Box-folder 15.9)
  - Williams, Jonathan, n.d. 1968 (Box-folder 15.10)
  - Wilson, May, n.d. 1971 (Box-folder 15.11)
  - W.O.R.K.S., n.d. 1973-1976 (Box-folder 15.12)
  - Xerox 1973, 1975 (Box-folder 15.13)
  - Y, n.d. (Box-folder 15.14)
  - Yinger (P. Spencer) 1970 (Box-folder 15.15)
  - Zabala, Horacio, n.d. 1973 (Box-folder 15.16)
  - Zack, David 1983 (Box-folder 15.17)
  - Zaj, n.d. (Box-folder 15.18)
  - Zimmers, Jon, n.d. (Box-folder 15.19)
- Series II: Book Art
  - For breakfast I'll have, oh, two slices of dry toast and a cup of hot water., n.d. (Box 15)
  - You know it has to be a hairpiece., n.d. (Box 15)
- Series III: Oversize Materials
  - Act or Fact Poster (2 posters), oversized (Box 1)
  - George Washington Envelope, oversized (Box 1)
  - Tempo, Sole, Amore, Terra Posters (2 red), oversized (Box 1)
  - Tempo, Sole, Amore, Terra Posters (2 yellow), oversized (Box 1)
  - Tempo, Sole, Amore, Terra Poster (1 blue), oversized (Box 1)
  - Maritime Poster with text, oversized (Box 1)
  - Anastasia and the Stairway Poster, oversized (Box 1)
  - Hand Broadside, oversized (Box 1)
  - Maritime Broadsides, oversized (Box 1)
  - Fran Shuuld Image 1972, oversized (Box 1)
  - Fran Shuuld Image, oversized (Box 1)
  - Water and Map Poster, oversized (Box 1)
  - Fan Light Window with Text, oversized (Box 1)
  - Men on a Stairway Poster, oversized (Box 1)
  - The Marcel Duchamp Fan Club, oversized (Box 1)
  - Ah...Do it Yourself Drawing, oversized (Box 1)
  - Stop...Tell me, How long did you? Collage, oversized (Box 1)
  - One Wheel Mouse Drawing, oversized (Box 1)
  - The Selected Spirit of human Life in hidden Landscapes Map, oversized (Box 1)
  - Do you Speak English?, oversized (Box 1)
  - Image by Signo Graphia II, oversized (Box 1)
  - Vilian Jakubik and Rudolf Sikora to the Traffic Participants, oversized (Box 1)
  - Triptych Trees by Elisabetta Gut (Box 1)
  - John Furnival Proposal for the Visualisation of a Sequence, oversized (Box 1)
  - Asian Photographs (2), oversized (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Photographs, oversized (Box 1)
  - German Newsprint, Die Welt June 10, 1971, oversized (Box 1)
  - An International Cyclopedia of Plans and Occurences (Box 1)
  - Fraternity, Class Conciliation, Liberty, Equality, oversized (Box 1)
  - 79 NQ, L, oversized (Box 1)
  - Three Proposals for a Junk Yard (3 images), oversized (Box 1)
  - Out of Town by Rudolf Sikora, oversized (Box 1)
  - Jan Steklik and Marianee Glass (3 photographs), oversized (Box 1)
  - Letter to Davi Det Hompson from Mirella Bentivoglio 1973, oversized (Box 1)
  - Crying Friend 1973, oversized (Box 1)
  - Joe Messinger Print, (with flocking) 1972 (Box 1)
  - 10 Xeroxed Views of Notre-Dame Cathedral, Montreal, from 1829-1972, oversized (Box 1)
  - An Exhibition of Re-Cycling, oversized (Box 1)
  - CAYC Alberto Pellegrino, oversized (Box 1)
  - Cherryville Liberation Set for Feb. 22, oversized (Box 1)
  - Salisbury To Become Versailles of Piedmont!, oversized (Box 1)
  - Zvolen 17, oversized (Box 1)
  - Carry a Koan in Your Bag (or pocket) 1967, 1972, oversized (Box 1)
  - Die Natur ist unser bester Braumeister, oversized (Box 1)
  - German Map, oversized (Box 1)
  - Pattengill Photograph, oversized (Box 1)
  - Official Navy Photograph, Office of Public Information, n.d., oversized (Box 1)
  - Achtung-ein Mensch Map, oversized (Box 1)
  - S pannen and Ent Collage, oversized (Box 1)